A Guide to the Thomas H. Hunter Collection 1934-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961, 4 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 91-17)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961-1963, 3 ALS (Box-folder 91-18)
- AN INAUGURAL BRIEF 1962/01/09, TMs (Box-folder 91-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1959-1968, TLS (P), TL, 32 TL (CC) (Box-folder 91-20)
  Personal Correspondence, To 1965 M
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1955-1968, 42 TLS (Box-folder 91-21)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960-1961, 2 ALS (Box-folder 91-22)
- CARL V. MOORE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/02/05, Telegram (Box-folder 91-23)
- PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE OF MISCELLANEOUS DOCUMENTS 1963/CA, 3 Photographs, B&W, 4x5; Photograph, B&W, 5x8 (Box-folder 91-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS, PAMPHLET, POSTCARD 1952-1965, 5 Reprints/Pamphlets, PC (Box-folder 91-25)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963-1965, 4 TLS/TL (CC) (Box-folder 91-26)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1960-1965, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 91-27)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1958-1965, 13 TL (CC) (Box-folder 91-28)
  Personal Correspondence, To 1965 N
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1959-1965, 12 TLS (Box-folder 91-29)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961/08/05, TL (CC) (Box-folder 91-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE AND ANNOUNCEMENT 1964/CA, AN, Printed Card (Box-folder 91-31)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1955-1965, 29 TLS (Box-folder 91-32)
  Personal Correspondence, To 1965 O, P, Q
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1955-1965, 38 TL (CC) (Box-folder 91-33)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1955-1961, 4 ALS (Box-folder 91-33)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1965, 2 Telegrams (Box-folder 91-35)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960-1965, 6 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 91-36)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1962-1963, 76 TL (CC) (Box-folder 91-37)
  Personal Correspondence, To 1965 Miscellaneous
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 45 TLS (Box-folder 91-38)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 9 ALS (Box-folder 91-39)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 3 AN (Box-folder 91-40)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 11 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 91-41)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962-1963, 7 TMs (P) (Box-folder 91-42)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1962-1963, 15 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 91-43)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARDS, NOTES, PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE 1962-1963/CA, 2 APCS, 3 AN, 3 Photographs, B&W; 2.5x3.5 (Box-folder 91-44)
- MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE N.D., 3 Photographs, B&W; 5x7, 7x9, 8x10 (Box-folder 91-45)
- MISCELLANEOUS ENVELOPES ADDRESSED TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 2 Envelopes (Box-folder 91-46)
- EXPERIMENTAL PHYSIOLOGY NOTEBOOK 1936, TMs (M) (Box-folder 92-1)
  Experimental Physiology, Course A - Lent Term, 1936 - Trinity Hall
- EXPERIMENTAL PHYSIOLOGY NOTEBOOK 1936, TMs (M) (Box-folder 92-2)
  Experimental Physiology, Course A - Easter Term, 1936 - Trinity Hall
- EXPERIMENTAL PHYSIOLOGY NOTEBOOK 1936/CA, TMs (M) (Box-folder 92-3)
  Experimental Physiology, Course B - Michelmas Term - Trinity Hall
- PATHOLOGY II NOTEBOOK 1936/CA, TMs (M) (Box-folder 92-4)
  Pathology II - Trinity Hall
- UNIDENTIFIED NOTEBOOK N.D., AMs (Box-folder 92-5)
- CONTENTS OF UNIDENTIFIED NOTEBOOK N.D., AMs (Box-folder 92-6)
- NEUROLOGY NOTES N.D., AMs (Box-folder 93-1)
  Neurology
- PATHOLOGY NOTES N.D., AMs (Box-folder 93-2)
  Pathology
- PLACENTA NOTES N.D., AMs (Box-folder 93-3)
  Placenta
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., AMs (Box-folder 93-4)
  Notes
- NOTEBOOK [NO CONTENTS] N.D., Binder (Box-folder 93-5)
  Notebook
- NOTEBOOK CONTENTS N.D., AMs (Box-folder 93-6)
- MEDICAL NOTEBOOK [NO CONTENTS] N.D., Binder (Box-folder 93-7)
  Medical Notebook
- MEDICAL NOTEBOOK CONTENTS N.D., AMs (Box-folder 93-8)
- MEDICAL NOTEBOOK [NO CONTENTS] N.D., Binder (Box-folder 94-1)
- MEDICAL NOTEBOOK CONTENTS N.D., AMs (Box-folder 94-2)
- NEUROLOGY NOTEBOOK [NO CONTENTS] N.D., Binder (Box-folder 94-3)
  Neurology Notebook
- NEUROLOGY NOTEBOOK CONTENTS N.D., AMs (Box-folder 94-4)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1970, Notebook (Box-folder 95-1)
  Appointment Books, 1970-1981
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1971, Notebook (Box-folder 95-2)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1972, Notebook (Box-folder 95-3)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1973, Notebook (Box-folder 95-4)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1974, Notebook (Box-folder 95-5)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1975, Notebook (Box-folder 95-6)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1976, Notebook (Box-folder 95-7)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1977, Notebook (Box-folder 95-8)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1978, Notebook (Box-folder 95-9)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1978-1979, Notebook (Box-folder 95-10)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1979-1980, Notebook (Box-folder 95-11)
- APPOINTMENT BOOK 1980-1981, Notebook (Box-folder 95-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTEBOOK N.D., AMs (Box-folder 96-1)
  Notebooks
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTEBOOK 1959-1960/CA, AMs (Box-folder 96-2)
- CHECKBOOK 1945-1946, Notebook (Box-folder 96-3)
  Checkbooks
- CHECKBOOK 1946-1947, Notebook (Box-folder 96-4)
- LEDGER 1962/CA, AMs (Box-folder 96-5)
  Ledger
- BACTERIAL ENDOCARDITIS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/03, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-1)
  Manuscripts
- BACTERIAL ENDOCARDITIS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/03, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-2)
- BACTERIAL ENDOCARDITIS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/03, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-3)
- ENDOCARDITIS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-4)
- ENDOCARDITIS (CECIL'S TEXTBOOK OF MEDICINE) BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND CHARTS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949/CA, AMs (Box-folder 97-6)
- ACTION OF PENICILLIN IN AN AMINO ACID-FREE MEDIUM BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-7)
- ACTION OF PENICILLIN IN AN AMINO ACID-FREE MEDIUM BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-8)
- THE TREATMENT OF BACTERIAL INFECTIONS OF THE HEART AND PERICARDIUM BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-9)
- NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., 2 AN (Box-folder 97-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS RE ENDOCARDITIS N.D., 2 Reprints (Box-folder 97-11)
- NOTES ON COMMITTEE ON INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS IN MEDICAL EDUCATION MEETING BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-12)
- NOTES RE PROF. EXPERT AND ROLE IN SOCIETY BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-13)
- NOTES RE MALARIA, ETC. BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-14)
- A REVISED SET OF VALUES FOR THE FUTURE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-15)
- LETTER TO THE EDITOR BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-16)
- WHAT ARE PRINCIPLES? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-17)
- THE FORBIDDEN EXPERIMENT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-18)
- ENDS AND MEANS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-19)
- ECOLOGY IN PERSPECTIVE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-20)
- MEDICAL ETHICS, NOT ETIQUETTE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-22)
- A SCHOOL OF PUBLIC AFFAIRS - SOLUTION OF A FALSE DICHOTOMY IN THE UNIVERSITIES BY THOMAS H.HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-23)
- NOTE ON PURPOSES OF THE UNIVERSITY BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-24)
- PRESENTATION FOR NAIROBI BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/02, AMs (Box-folder 97-25)
- THE WEDGE, SLIPPERY SLOPE, CAMEL'S NOSE IN THE TENT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-26)
- MEDICAL ETHICS, NOT ETIQUETTE N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-27)
- CRISIS MENTALITY BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-28)
- COMMUNICATION GAP - 2 CULTURES REVISITED BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-29)
- DEPROFESSIONALIZING THE PROFESSION 1976/02/05, Reprint (Box-folder 97-30)
- APOLLO AND THE ENVIRONMENT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-31)
  Speeches and Papers
- CENTERS FOR THE SURVIVAL OF CIVILIZATION? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971/CA, TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-32)
- CENTERS FOR THE SURVIVAL OF CIVILIZATION? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971/07, Reprint (Box-folder 97-33)
- ON LETTING DIE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-34)
- PERSONALITY, ATTITUDINAL, AND SOCIAL CORRELATES OF DRUG USE BY RUBEN ORIVE AND HAROLD B. GERARD N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-35)
- HUMAN RIGHTS AND FOREIGN POLICY 1977/05/16, AN, TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-36)
- HUMANHOOD - ESSAYS IN BIOMEDICAL ETHICS INTRODUCTION BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-37)
- THE COMMUNICATIONS GAP IN BIOMEDICAL ETHICS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-38)
- THE COMMUNICATIONS GAP IN BIOMEDICAL ETHICS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-39)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS OF ARTICLES BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961-1977, 12 Reprints (Box-folder 97-40)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1975-1978, 9 Reprints (Box-folder 97-41)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1958-1965, 6 TLS, TMs (Box-folder 97-43)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-44)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES PRESIDENTIAL ADDRESS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960/10/31, TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-45)
- BOYS IN WHITE - REVIEW BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-46)
- BOYS IN WHITE - REVIEW BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-47)
- BOYS IN WHITE - REVIEW BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-48)
- ADDRESS TO THE ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-49)
- PRESIDENT'S WELCOME BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 2 TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-50)
- PREFACE FOR 1959 ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES TEACHING INSTITUTE REPORT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-51)
- TALK FOR THE NATIONAL FUND FOR MEDICAL EDUCATION BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-52)
- COMPENSATION OF CLINICAL FACULTY AT THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-53)
- SCHOOL OF MEDICINE, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA N.D., TMs (Box-folder 97-54)
- TEACHING CLINICAL MEDICINE IN THE UNITED STATES BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 2 TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-55)
- HEALTH CARE MANPOWER: SOME SHIFTS IN EMPHASIS BETWEEN TEACHING AND RESEARCH IN OUR MEDICAL SCHOOLS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 97-56)
- THE CHANGING RESPONSIBILITIES OF THE HOSPITAL FOR THE GRADUATE EDUCATION OF PHYSICIANS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/05/20, TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-57)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE, REPRINT, NEWSCLIPPINGS 1964-1965, ANS, 7 Reprints/Newsclippings (Box-folder 97-58)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1975, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 97-59)
  Talks
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975, 11 TLS (Box-folder 97-60)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMOS 1975, 2 TM (Box-folder 97-61)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENT AND INVOICE 1975, TMs (P), Printed Form (Box-folder 97-62)
- NOTES RE PROPER HEALTH CARE AFTER RETIREMENT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 97-63)
- A PRE-RETIREMENT EDUCATIONAL SEMINAR 1975/06/05, TMs (P) (Box-folder 97-64)
- MEETING AGENDA 1976/05/12, Pamphlet (Box-folder 97-65)
- ROBERT J. GLASER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966/05/09, TLS (Box-folder 98-1)
  Notes and Preliminary Manuscripts of Talks
- MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE OF THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 2 Photographs, B&W; 7.5x8.5 (Box-folder 98-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS AND PAMPHLETS 1964-1971, 12 Newsclippings, 2 Pamphlets (Box-folder 98-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS TABLES 1965-1966, 3 TMs (P), AMS (Box-folder 98-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 30 AN (Box-folder 98-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 7 AN (Box-folder 98-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARDS 1965/CA, TPC, TPCS (Box-folder 98-7)
- HOSPITAL TRAINING PROGRAMS IN THE VARIOUS SPECIALTIES BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 98-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 98-9)
- THE CHANGING RESPONSIBILITIES OF THE HOSPITAL FOR THE GRADUATE EDUCATION OF PHYSICIANS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 98-10)
- NATURE OF DISEASE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 98-11)
- ON CONSULTING ABROAD BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 98-12)
- CONCLUSIONS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 98-13)
- A MISSION IN MEDICAL EDUCATION TO THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/CA, TMs (Box-folder 98-14)
- A MISSION IN MEDICAL EDUCATION TO THE UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/CA, TMs (P)/AMs (Box-folder 98-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE 1965/CA, 6 Photographs, B&W; 3.5x5, An Envelope (Box-folder 98-16)
- A REVISED SET OF VALUES FOR THE FUTURE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 98-17)
- BIBLIOGRAPHY N.D., TMs (Box-folder 98-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1963-1965, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 98-19)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978-1979, 9 TLS (Box-folder 98-20)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS AND TALKS 1979/CA, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 98-21)
- NOTES RE WORCESTER TALK BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 98-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND 1980/CA, 11 AMs (Box-folder 98-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1974-1980, 16 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 98-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1975, 13 TL (CC) (Box-folder 98-25)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975, 2 TLS (Box-folder 98-26)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975, 3 ALS (Box-folder 98-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE OF THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 4 Photographs, Color; 3.5x5 (Box-folder 98-28)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1969-1977, 14 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 98-29)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975-1977, 5 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 98-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL N.D., 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 98-31)
- THE PURSUIT OF HAPPINESS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 98-32)
- ECOLOGY IN PERSPECTIVE BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (Box-folder 98-33)
- LECTURE AND TALK NOTES AND OUTLINES 1975-1977/CA, 44 AN (Box-folder 98-34)
- LECTURE AND TALK NOTES AND OUTLINES 1975-1977/CA, 17 AMs (Box-folder 98-35)
- A PHILOSOPHY OF CLINICAL RESEARCH BASED ON NEED BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-1)
  Reprints, Talks, Papers
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969-1970, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1964-1977, 30 Reprints (Box-folder 99-3)
- HOW MANY HATS CAN A HOUSE OFFICER WEAR? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976/CA, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 99-4)
  How Many Hats Can a House Officer Wear?
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO THE EDITOR, NEW ENGLAND JOURNAL OF MEDICINE 1976/04/29, AMs, TL (Box-folder 99-5)
- RESPONSE TO CORRESPONDENCE RE HOW MANY HATS CAN A HOUSE OFFICER WEAR? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976/CA, AMs (Box-folder 99-6)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1976, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 99-7)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976, 5 TLS, 2 TLS (CC) (Box-folder 99-8)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976, 4 ALS (Box-folder 99-9)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976, 4 TLS (P) (Box-folder 99-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1952-1980, 11 Reprints (Box-folder 99-11)
  Reprints
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT S. GOODHART 1977/05/25, TL (CC) (Box-folder 99-12)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977, 4 TLS (Box-folder 99-13)
- COMMENTS ON THE SYMPOSIUM ON ETHICAL CONCEPTS IN MODERN MEDICAL EDUCATION, AND RELATED MATTERS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/10/13, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-14)
- A PHILOSOPHY OF CLINICAL RESEARCH BASED ON NEEDS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-15)
- THE NEED FOR COOPERATION IN PROVIDING BASIC HEALTH SERVICES BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-16)
- FREDERICK MOSHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, MUTANT C.P.C.'S? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER AND JOSEPH FLETCHER 1971/CA, TM (P)/2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1950-1971, 11 Reprints (Box-folder 99-18)
- PAGE PROOFS FOR COMMENTS ON THE SYMPOSIUM BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/CA, Reprint (Box-folder 99-19)
- JUST SHORT OF CHAOS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/01, Reprint (Box-folder 99-20)
- CENTERS FOR THE SURVIVAL OF CIVILIZATION? BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971/07, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-21)
  Publications and Reprints
- APOLLO AND THE ENVIRONMENT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 99-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS OF ARTICLES BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1978, 9 Reprints (Box-folder 99-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1961-1977, 4 Reprints (Box-folder 99-24)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 100-1)
  Miscellany, Foldered
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 100-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS 1962, 2 Pamphlets (Box-folder 100-3)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO FRIENDS OF BUFFY AND BILL PARSON N.D., 2 TM (Box-folder 100-4)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980, 3 TL, 8 TLS (Box-folder 100-5)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 2 ALS (Box-folder 100-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1978, Reprint (Box-folder 100-7)
- MEMO AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 3 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 100-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL N.D., 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 100-9)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER AND MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1980/CA, ALS (P), 2 AN (Box-folder 100-10)
- ANNIE G. LIPSCOMB TO FRANCIS BOYER 1963/02/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 100-11)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 2 TLS (Box-folder 100-12)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962/CA, 2 ALS (Box-folder 100-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1960-1962, 6 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 100-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENT, NOTES, RECEIPT N.D., Printed Card, 3 AN, Printed Form (Box-folder 100-15)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962/09/25, TL (CC) (Box-folder 100-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1961/CA, 7 TMs (P) (Box-folder 100-17)
- CHUCK YOUNG TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1959/09/07, AN, ALS (Box-folder 100-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1962/CA, AN (Box-folder 100-19)
- UNTITLED PAPER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 100-20)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1954-1962, 6 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 100-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 100-22)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1962-1963, 40 TL (CC) (Box-folder 100-23)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 9 TLS (Box-folder 100-24)
- RECEIPTS 1962, 2 Printed Forms (Box-folder 100-25)
- NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND 1963/04/19, AMsS (Box-folder 100-26)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 100-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962, 2 TMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 100-28)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO GEORGE R. MINOR 1973, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 100-29)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971, 2 TLS (Box-folder 100-30)
- GEORGE R. MINOR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/11/26, ALS (Box-folder 100-31)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971, 3 TL (CC/P) (Box-folder 100-32)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971, 3 TMs (P), TMs (Box-folder 100-33)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CAROL J. JOHNS 1981/12/22, TL (P) (Box-folder 101-1)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 6 TLS (Box-folder 101-2)
- ALHASAN CEESAY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981/10/27, ALS (Box-folder 101-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., AN (Box-folder 101-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1981/04, Pamphlet (Box-folder 101-5)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 2 TL (P) (Box-folder 101-6)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981/11/09, Envelope (Box-folder 101-7)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 2 TLS, ALS (Box-folder 101-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1981, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 101-9)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 4 TLS (Box-folder 101-10)
- MIKE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981/12/28, ALS (Box-folder 101-11)
- MISCELLANEOUS BILLS AND RECEIPTS 1981, 33 Printed Forms (Box-folder 101-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1974/CA, AN (Box-folder 101-13)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1981, 3 TM, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 101-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSCLIPPINGS 1968-1972, 10 Reprints/Newsclippings (Box-folder 101-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., AN (P), 6 AN (Box-folder 101-16)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972, 2 TM (P), TM (Box-folder 101-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971, TMs (P) (Box-folder 101-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1964, 10 TMs (P) (Box-folder 101-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1963-1964, 3 Reprints (Box-folder 101-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JUNTA DIRECTIVA 1963/06/12, TL (CC) (Box-folder 102-1)
  Miscellany, Unfoldered
- GABRIEL VELAZQUEZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963/02/19, AMS (Box-folder 102-2)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1980, 2 ALS (Box-folder 102-2)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963, 2 TM (P) (Box-folder 102-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1963/CA, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 102-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS 1962, 2 Pamphlets (Box-folder 102-5)
- ROBERT W. SCHRIER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1985/11/15, TL (Box-folder 102-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1956-1982, 5 Reprints (Box-folder 102-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL N.D., 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 102-9)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER; CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER; COPYRIGHT AGREEMENTS 1985, 2 TLS, 2 Printed Forms, 3 TLS (P) (Box-folder 102-10)
- LETTER DRAFT IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., AMs (Box-folder 102-11)
- JIM CRAIG TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980/11/12, AMS (Box-folder 102-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSLETTERS 1980-1984, 4 Reprints/Newsletters (Box-folder 102-13)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1983-1986, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 102-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1979/CA, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 102-15)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1983-1985, 2 TLS (Box-folder 102-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1982-1987, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 102-17)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1983-1985/CA, 3 Envelopes (Box-folder 102-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARDS N.D., 15 PC, PC Book (Box-folder 102-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARDS N.D., 52 PC (Box-folder 102-20)
- HENRY CHAUNCEY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/06/12, TLS (Box-folder 103-1)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1957-1973, 6 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 103-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972-1980/CA, 2 TMs/3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 103-3)
- STUDENT GRADES N.D., AN (Box-folder 103-4)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/CA, 2 TM (Box-folder 103-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOSEPH FLETCHER 1974-1976, 15 TL (CC) (Box-folder 103-6)
- [MARY B. WAGNER] TO JOSEPH FLETCHER 1974-1976, 20 TL (CC), TLS (Box-folder 103-7)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 194-1976, 40 TLS (Box-folder 103-8)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1974, 11 ALS (Box-folder 103-9)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARY B. WAGNER 1973-1975, 24 TLS, TPCS, 3 ALS (Box-folder 103-10)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARTHA NELSON 1976, TPCS, 3 TLS (Box-folder 103-11)
- MRS. JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARY B. WAGNER 1973/06/17, ALS (Box-folder 103-12)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1976, 10 TL (CC), 4 TLS (Box-folder 103-13)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1976, 6 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 103-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND ANNOUNCEMENTS 1973-1984/CA, 4 AN, 2 Printed Cards (Box-folder 103-15)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 3 APCS, TPC (Box-folder 103-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS MICROFORM AND NEGATIVES N.D., Microform, 2 Negatives (Box-folder 103-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS AND NEWSCLIPPINGS 1962-1975, 12 Newletters/Newsclippings (Box-folder 103-18)
- ELECTROCARDIOGRAPHY SYLLABUS N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 103-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 103-20)
- [MARY B. WAGNER] TO JOSEPH FLETCHER 1973, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 103-21)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 6 TLS (Box-folder 103-22)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARY B. WAGNER 1973, 6 TLS (Box-folder 103-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPING N.D., Newsclipping (Box-folder 103-24)